[
    [
        {
            "question": "TAVR is an established treatment modality for:",
            "options":[
                "Severe Aortic valve stenosis",
                "Severe Coronary artery stenosis",
                "Repairing a thoracic aneurysm"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Full form of TAVR is:",
            "options":[
                "Transcaval Aortic Vascular Repair",
                "Transcatheter Aortic Valve Replacement",
                "Transfemoral Artery Vascular Repair"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Benefits of TAVR:",
            "options":[
                "Non-Surgical",
                "Faster Recovery",
                "No Chest Scars",
                "Faster discharge",
                "All of above",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "Diagnostic tests for Severe Aortic stenosis include:",
            "options":[
                "ECHO",
                "ECG",
                "CT Scan",
                "MRI", 
                "Options 1,2,3", 
                "Options 2,3,4",
                "All of above",
                "None of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 4
        },
        {
            "question": "Brand name of First Indian TAVR Device:",
            "options":[
                "Myvalve",
                "Myval",
                "Meres",
                "Biomime"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }

    ],

    [
        {
            "question": "Meril is the First Indian company in the world to launch a Non-Surgical Aortic valve replacement therapy:",
            "options":[
                "Yes",
                "No"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Merilâ€™s Myval THV is CE Approved and launched in Europe, true or false?:",
            "options":[
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Latest clinical data suggests, TAVR is now a preferred therapy for following patients with Severe Aortic Valve Stenosis who also are:",
            "options":[
                "High risk to Surgery",
                "Intermediate risk to Surgery",
                "Low risk to Surgery",
                "All of above",
                "None of above"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "USP Tag line of Myval is:",
            "options":[
                "Preference for heart",
                "Precision at heart",
                "Live your life",
                "Future is here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Most of the patients get discharged on 3rd day after TAVR procedure, true or false?",
            "options":[
                "True",
                "False"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }

    ]
]
